<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Prank Sounds</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!-- Splash Screen   -->

    <!-- Policy Screen   -->
    <string name="policy_start_button">Start</string>
    <string name="policy_detail">
        I want to inform you that whenever you use my Service, in a case of an error in the app I
        collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data.
        This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address,
        device name,operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing my Service,
        the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.\n\nCookies\n\nCookies are files
        with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are
        sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored on your device’s internal
        memory.\n\nThis Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly.However, the app may use third
        party code and libraries that use “cookies” to collect information and improve their services.
        You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent
        to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions
        of this Service.\n\nService Providers\n\nI may employ third-party companies and individuals due to
        the following reasons:\n\nI may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised
        to review this page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting
        the new Privacy Policy on this page.\n\nContact Us\nIf you have any questions or suggestions about
        my Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact me
    </string>

    <!--   Home screen -->
    <string name="home_screen">Home Fragment</string>
    <string name="prank_hair_cutting">Hair Cutting</string>
    <string name="prank_broken_screen">Broken Screen</string>
    <string name="prank_call_screen">Call Screen</string>
    <string name="prank_sound_funny">Sound Funny</string>
    <string name="prank_taser_prank">Taser Prank</string>
    <string name="prank_setting">Settings</string>

</resources>

